touropia.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Touropia

**Introduction**  
This Site collects non-personally identifiable data (your IP address, how often you visit our site, which pages you visit, etc.) each time you visit touropia.com. We use this information to make the site better and easier to use.

This Site does not collect personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals, which can occur in a variety of contexts. This information might be used for promotions, specials, or to contact you when you have a question. You are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

**Cookies**  
This Site uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of text that are written to your hard drive by your browser to store information about. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to enable or disable cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to disable cookies if you prefer. Disabling cookies, however, may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**External Web Sites**  
This privacy policy only applies to this web site. The web site may contain links to external web sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any other web sites you may visit through the web site. The inclusion of links to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites nor any association with their owners or operators. If you have any complaints relating to such sites, please contact them directly.

**Changes**  
As our Site continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Site. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately.
